anata o kinde tashikametai
I want to cut into you and see for myself
mitai
I want to see
migaita kiri tana no ue
There, on the polished paulownia shelf,
saite
sliced up
narabete
lined up
soko ni atashi wa sunderu
Is that where I live now?
atashi no katahou wa ikiteru
Is my other half alive?
osaetara kowai
Are you afraid to be held down?
sukoshi Zutsudakara
It's okay, I'll take it slow
kiri hiraite mune ni
I only want to cut you open
shita o hasetai dakenano
and run my tongue along your heart
soto wa uttori to toumei ni sumashita maku
Outside is the alluring, see-through skin;
uchi wa kuro murasaki iro ni nekki o obite
the inside tinged with dark purple fervor...
This is going be a warning
I wish you could stop complaining a long time ago
Now, I will go where ever I want to get my right place in my life
I am ready to fight
Every memory I remembered
communicated with each other in my world
But something or someone schemes to lead me somewhere wrong
I have to a have strong mind and soul
I will not be a fake to you, I swear
I'll never be a fake to the people who I love
I'll never show you the real, if you make me hate you
I can't be a fake to myself
This is going to be a last chance
All your excuses are not working anymore
Every memory I remembered
communicated with each other in my world
But something or someone schemes to lead me somewhere wrong
I have to a have strong mind and soul
I will not be a fake to you, I swear
I'll never be a fake to the people who I love
I'll never show you the real, if you make me hate you
I can't be a fake to myself